

Van Jerson C. Soria

WEB DEVELOPER









A career shifter with a 3 years of experience in Manufacturing and Logictics company. And now a creative Web Developer / Web Designer who is passionate about everything that goes into developing websites and applications.

https://web-portfolio-vanjerson.vercel.app 09068069596 vanjerson2@gmail.com

Sitio Atisan, Brgy. Talaan-pantoc.

Sariaya, Quezon 4322

Hard Skills

- Front-End (ReactJs, WordPress)
- Back-End (Php, Laravel, MySql, PhpMyAdmin)
- Web Design (Adobe Photoshop, Figma)
- Version Control
- Content Creating / Editing
- · MS Office

Soft Skills

- Critical Thinking
- Willingness to learn and trainability
- Can work under pressure
- Quick learner

Experience

Manufacturing Engineer

OPEN DATE ASIA INC. (2019 - 2020)

- Finalize the quality and design of products before sending to customers.
- Providing research, complete documentations, project plans and reports and give suggestions to improve products and downtime.
- Interact with customers to address their concerns, answer their questions and assist them with their needs.

Dispatch Supervisor

WARBUCKS SOUTHERN CORP (2020-2021)

- Providing Technical Documentation and Reports regarding deliveries and receiving of the products.
- Supervise and organize the team to make the operations more productive.

Education

Bachelor of Science in Computer Engineering

AMA Computer College Lucena City Campus - 2014 - 2019 (Graduated)

Certification

Full Stack Web Development

KodeGo Bootcamp

(November 2022 - March 2023)

Projects

GameHub - Multi-page Website

- · Uses HTML and CSS to create the website
- One page that uses HTML form

GameHub - Interactive Website

 Uses HTML, CSS, Javascript, Form validation and Web API

G-Hub - Full-stack Ecommerce Website

- · Uses PHP for front-end and back-end
- MySql for Database